https://www.justfundraising.com/privacy-policy

USA
Canada
Just Fundraising
1-888-440-4114CONTACT US
0item(s)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Tips To Raise More
Search:
Home
Order-Takers
Cookie DoughNuts & SnacksCandlesFace MasksBest Online Fundraising Ideas For Schools And TeamsPopcornHoliday ShoppersPretzelsPizzaCheesecakeCoffeeEnvironmentalFlowers
Scratch Cards
Scratch & HelpVictory Scratch
Discount Cards
Dinner And Movie CardRestaurant.com CardsLocal Discount Cards
Fundraising Samples
Candy Fundraisers
Candy BarsFortune CookiesLollipopsPretzel Rod Fundraisers - $1 and $2 RodsJack Link's SticksWelch's & Gummies
T-Shirt Fundraiser
Your Group Type
School
Sports
Non-Profit
Church
Toolbox
Step-By-Step Fundraising Guide
Privacy Policy
Product was successfully added to your shopping cart.
Go to cart page
Continue
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us.
It is JustFundraising's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. JustFundraising may change this privacy policy from time to time at JustFundraising's sole discretion.
Get Your FREE CatalogIncludes Sample Brochures & Info
Order-Takers
Cookie Dough
Nuts & Snacks
Candles
Face Masks
Online Fundraising
Popcorn
Order-Takers
Cookie DoughNuts & SnacksCandlesFace MasksBest Online Fundraising Ideas For Schools And TeamsPopcornHoliday ShoppersPretzelsPizzaCheesecakeCoffeeEnvironmentalFlowers
Scratch Cards
Scratch & HelpVictory Scratch
Discount Cards
Dinner And Movie CardRestaurant.com CardsLocal Discount Cards
Fundraising Samples
Candy Fundraisers
Candy BarsFortune CookiesLollipopsPretzel Rod Fundraisers - $1 and $2 RodsJack Link's SticksWelch's & Gummies
Need Help?
©Copyright 2020 by JustFundraising. All Rights Reserved. Peruse the Terms & Privacy.
Follow or Contact Us On:
Code:
